thalamus.co 2019-05-01

# Thalamus Privacy Policy

Thalamus, Inc (“us”, “we”, “our” or the “Service”) operates  https://www.thalamus.co/ (the “Site”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of this site. 

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service, accessible at  https://www.thalamus.co/terms

## WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

### Information Collection and Use

We collect information from you when you register on our site.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: full name, email address, job role, and link to your personal website/LinkedIn profile, phone number, geographic location, and registration time (“Personal Information”). You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

After you have registered on the site, other information we may collect includes, but is not limited to: search and filter queries performed , content viewed, and links clicked on the Site.

### Using the Service

Furthermore, we collect information about which keywords you type into the search bar for the Service, but store them only in aggregate. We also collect information about any interactions on the Service, including, but not limited to: data viewed, bookmarks made, buttons clicked, search and filter queries performed, and advertising partner data inputted.

### Log Data

We also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

### Cookies

Cookies are files with small amounts of data, which include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.

## WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience   
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 
  * To improve our website   
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 
  * To improve customer service   
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 
  * To send periodic emails
  * To be shared with sponsored advertising partner(s) and/or business partner(s) when there is potential of a mutually beneficial relationship
  * To be shared with participating advertising partner(s) in their analytics dashboard and/or analytics email notifications

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, be sent to Thalamus sponsored advertising partner(s) and/or business partner(s), and/or other requests or questions.

## HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

With respect to any documents or data you choose to upload/add to Thalamus, we take the privacy and confidentiality of such documents and data seriously. We store all documents and data securely on our servers, and employ industry standard techniques to protect against unauthorized modifications of that data about you or your company, including personal information.

## DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information, other than to sponsored advertising partner(s) and/or business partner(s) of whom we have a financial relationship with. We also may share portions of your personally identifiable information, such as your job role, company email domain, first name and last name initial, with participating advertising partner(s) in their analytics dashboard and/or analytics email notifications. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

Thalamus shares anonymous data with Google Analytics, such as browser type, demographics, language settings, page views, time/date, and personal data with Sendgrid, specifically names and email addresses. Thalamus may also share your data with sponsored advertising partner(s) and/or business partner(s) of whom we have a financial relationship with. This data may include, but is not limited to, your personally identifiable information such as full name, job role, location, phone number, email address, and also your behaviors on the Site including, but not limited to: search and filter queries performed, content viewed, and links clicked. 

Thalamus has engaged Intercom to communicate in real-time with visitors on the Thalamus website. Doing so authorizes Inspectlet to use cookies and other tracking technologies, which may use the Personal Information of Thalamus' users. Such data is stored for a period of nine (9) months, and may include user data such as: Name, Email, Web Sessions, Last Seen, First Seen, Sign up Date, City and Country, IP Address, Last Contacted, Browser Language, Browser Version, and any messages sent between a Thalamus Chat Operator and the User. Such access to and use of Personal Information by Intercom is governed by Intercom's [Privacy Policy](https://www.inspectlet.com/legal#privacy). 

We may also share some basic information with advertising vendors through our proprietary analytics tool(s), but this will only include your job role, geographic location, and email domain, and first name, and last name initial. This proprietary analytics tool(s) may come in the form of a dashboard that an advertising partner can log into, or an email notifying them that certain logged-in users have viewed their advertising partner profile, or have performed certain buyer activities, which may include, but are not limited to: search and filter queries performed, content viewed, and links clicked. 

### Third Party Sponsors

If you have elected to register on the Thalamus Site, we may share your information (including Personally Identifiable Information) with sponsored advertising partner(s) and/or business partner(s) we have a financial relationship with. You agree that these business partner(s) and/or sponsored advertising partner(s) may use your Personally Identifiable Information to contact you, if they choose to provide you additional information regarding their products or services. 

### Displaying Your Data

If you are a registered Advertising Partner, any data entered or documents uploaded onto the Service may be displayed on the Service. You agree to have full knowledge that the Service is freely available to other Advertising Partners, who have access to your public information on the Service. We do not take responsibility for the privacy practices of other Advertising Partners or users who may use uploaded information and data for their own purposes.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### International Users

By using this Service, you incontestably agree that your data shall be transferred to the United States of America.

By choosing to become a registered member, or even an anonymous user of the Service, you agree that any dispute over privacy and our terms contained within this Privacy Policy will be governed by the law within the State of California, and the arbitration of any disputes arising in connection with Thalamus, Inc or the Service will be in accordance with our Terms of Service.

If you are visiting the Service from the European Union or other regions in the world with different laws than the United States concerning data collection and use, you agree that you are aware of the transference of your information to the United States. By providing any information you consent to any transfer and processing of your data in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### In the event of a Merger, Sale, or other Asset Transfer

If Thalamus is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, we will continue to ensure the confidentiality of any personal information and give affected users notice before personal information is transferred or becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at https://www.thalamus.co/terms

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our websites' privacy policy

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. We urge you to bookmark this Privacy Policy page and check it periodically if you are concerned about how your information is being used.

This policy was last modified on May 28th, 2018

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Thalamus, Inc

795 Folsom Street

San Francisco, CA 94103
